Now we need to update the Web page files in order to display the time.
So let's start off at the top of index HTML and under the header here.
Let's add a new Div ID.
And call it local time.
And now let's close it.
And also create a horizontal rule.
And then inside the div, let's create an H2 for S&P time synchronization.
And then make a label for.
For local time.
And right, connect to Wi-Fi.
Then let's close the label.
Then let's create a divide.
For the local time.
And then close the divide.
So that takes care of our label and our divide for local time.
So now we can update the styling and apt at CSIS.
So let's come here and copy this one.
And let's just paste it up here.
And let's change it to local time.
And that's it.
So now we can go to D.J.s.
And now go to the top of the file within the very function.
And we'll call the new function here.
And call it start local time interval.
OK, so now let's copy this, because we're going to define it at the bottom of the file.
And here that's comment that this function sets the interval.
For displaying local time.
Right function.
Start local time interval.
And then he will use the set interval.
And then we'll set the interval to call a function to get the local time, and we'll call it get local
time.
And we'll call it every 10 seconds.
OK, so now let's go to find it.
And this function gets the local time.
And I'll make a note.
And say connect the ESP 30 to.
To the internet.
And the time will be updated.
And then right function.
Get local time.
And then here will use get Jason.
And we'll say forward slash local time.
That, Jason.
Comma function.
Data.
And open the curly braces, and he will specify or divide.
Local time.
And then say that text.
And it's time.
OK, and then close it with the semicolon.
And that's it, and that's all for the Web page programming.
And in the next lesson, we'll continue with the FTP seven.